hashtagify.me 2013-06-07

# Hashtagify.me - Search And Find The Best Twitter Hashtags - Free

CyBranding Ltd. (hereafter “the Website Owner”) is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected, and this privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give the Website Owner when you use the hashtagify.me and CyBranding.com websites.

**We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so**. Upon registration, we will ask you if we can use your personal information to send you promotional information about our offers or about relevant third parties offers. You can always change your choice later in your account settings.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address and phone number
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
  * access and usage data from our website and service logs

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping
  * Compliance with our payment services providers policies
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services
  * We may use the information to send you relevant offers, if you opted in when signing up and didn’t opt out later

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. The Website Owner uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of the Website Owner’s websites, and their website access preferences. hashtagify.me and CyBranding.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using these websites, with the drawback that certain features of the websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by the Website Owner. and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

The Website Owner may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

### Change log

  * 30 December 2012 - Published
